You know, it's funny. I keep seeing people say things like, you're always online.
And I kind of chuckle at that because they're basically saying, you work from home and you take the time to tap in with us.
So good morning, everyone, or, you know, just morning.
So I'm currently shipping orders.
I always think it's good to come on and show you all that small operations doesn't mean they're inconsequential.
Because we really are like really tricked into thinking that if shit isn't like coming out of a major warehouse or if you don't have some great crazy stock or whatever that, you know, you're not doing nothing.
But I sit here and I fulfill your orders.
This person ordered five art prints.
Okay, like I did.
I painted. These are paintings.
There's five of them.
It comes with stickers.
They come in this nifty little reusable envelope.
And, you know, it's it's my art.
And I think a lot of us who are artists out here, we are so bamboozled.
We're so bamboozled into thinking that if we're not in Target or something, that we are not doing anything really valuable.
Don't believe that.
Please don't believe the hype.
And to be quite honest, you know, so much of our livelihood is spent working so hard for getting very little.
So you might as well get the same amount doing something that brings you joy.
One, two.
You feel me?
Zach, I'm going to need you for backgrounds soon.
And so I just want you to know, I'll be bringing you right on up to Nyack to sing some backgrounds into a microphone.
I don't know why I'm acting like I can see.
I can't see anything.
Hold on.
Okay.
Y'all ready for a little story time?
Yesterday, I was trying to be a responsible adult.
And I said, I'm going to go and get my oil changed because the light keeps coming on that says, get your oil changed.
So I said, yeah, I should do that.
And so I saw that there was a instant oil change place.
And I was like, oh, wow.
Never noticed that before.
But now that I see it, I should go.
So I went to the instant oil change place.
It was not instant.
Okay.
Thank you, Carmela.
I'm glad that we can support you in any way possible.
For real.
Like, you're not the first.
And we hope that you are the last to suffer deed theft.
And they're waiting 20 minutes.
And I was like, well, I don't have time to wait any longer.
Oh, I'm going to have to go because I had a class.
I mean, I had a call.
So I start to reverse.
And I accidentally reverse into the oil changers car.
Not my proudest moment.
Now, did I like, no, it was more of like a soft crunch.
But it was a crunch nonetheless.
So I immediately park up and hop out to give my insurance information and, you know, talk to the dude.
So it's a Haitian guy.
And he's like, oh.
Now, let me also add, though, this bumper has already been through some things.
Okay.
Anyway, so he exacerbated what had already been an issue.
It doesn't make it better, but I'm just saying.
So I don't know why you're assuming that I was rushing.
I wasn't rushing.
I just made a mistake.
So now I'm like, yes, I am packing the art.
So now, you know, he's taking a picture of the damage and says, I'm going to call 9-1-1.
Excuse me?
I said, why are you calling 9-1-1?
You need to report this to your insurance.
Well, it's going to take too long to report to my insurance.
I said, so what you think the cops are going to do?
And he was like, no, I'm calling 9-1-1.
And I was like, well, I'm going to tell you right now.
I'm not going to be here when they get here.
Because I'm not sitting here to wait for no cops because I didn't break no law.
Okay.
I didn't commit no crime.
So I'm about to go.
You have all the information you need.
So I skate off.
Now, I get to the house.
And I am very, very tapped into my intuition.
So I was about to go back there.
And my intuition literally said, stay yo ass in this motherfucking house.
And I had just swam that morning and did an hour of Qigong.
So my energy and clarity was very, very high.
Okay.
I did not leave the scene of an accident.
I provided my insurance information to the person.
And I provided my license plate because he got a picture of it.
And there was no one harmed.
Hey, Walter.
So no, I did not leave the scene of an accident.
It's no different than if I'm in a Target parking lot.
Y'all just be running your mouth saying all type of things on this app.
Anywho.
So, so Abby, I'm going to get there because that's the part right there.
Why do you want to involve the cops?
What is the validity of the police in this situation?
I did not.
There was no traffic violation.
So let me just tell you, had I caused the accident by doing a traffic violation, you call the cops.
It sucks.
However, that is a necessity because you need the police to come and be like, oh, yeah, you was wrong and put it in a report.
In this situation, I'm not saying I'm not wrong.
So I'm not sure what.
And as a Haitian man, I'm also looking at you like, why are you bringing the cops in?
At this time, in this era of world, why would you even bring in the cops in?
And you're right.
In L.A., you exchange info and keep it pushing if no one's hurt.
Listen, I had a lady hit me in L.A.
And we got out the car and she was exchanging information with me and everything.
And then I could tell she was struggling.
She didn't fuck up my car, so it was nothing.
But I could tell she was struggling.
And I said, you good?
And she was like, I mean, my mom has cancer and I'm just trying to navigate that.
And I said, come on in.
And I gave her a long hug.
And she started crying in my arms.
Not Karen White Lady crying, like caring person crying.
And then I sent her on her way.
And then I went on one of the worst dates ever.
Anywho, um, so now I head to the house.
I had a call that I had to get to.
So I go to the house and I get a call.
I do the call.
Then I finish the call and I get a text from my neighbor who's a down-ass white girl.
And the text says, hey, girl, do you need backup?
There's three cops outside your house.
This motherfucker sent the cops to my house.
This nigga sent the cops to my house.
The cops was outside my house.
Thankfully, the main cop was decent enough, at least in speaking.
And he was like, I opened the door and literally said, are y'all here for this thing to say hello?
Are y'all here for this thing?
And he said, yeah, we needed to confirm that the driver of the vehicle is the insured.
I said, they sent three of you to my home for that question.
He said, well, when we leave a town, we have to have backup.
I said, what town did you leave?
So he named this other town.
Mind you, I was four minutes from my house.
So I didn't even know that that was a town line that I had crossed.
Nonetheless, I said, wow.
I said, let me tell you, I have never in my entire life.
And I've been driving since I was 15.
Call the cops in any accident that I've been in.
And he said, yeah, because most people just work it out.
So he also was like, now, hold on.
Is somebody in here talking madness?
Cops went to her house and she said she didn't feel it.
And he was like, man, you're in a two ton car.
You wouldn't have felt it.
I was hit on foot by a white woman in the SUV and she blamed me for being on my phone and drove off.
Got it.
So I said, you know, you don't waste your time.
Well, he was like, well, the card that you showed him was expired, but we ran your plates and you have insurance.
I know I have insurance.
Yes.
And he was like, so I just have to give you this card because it says that a police report was done.
And I said, so y'all didn't come over here and waste your time.
And he was like, we're on till midnight.
So it is what it is.
But he was very pleasant, thankfully, because y'all know I don't fuck with the car.
I don't, I don't, I don't at all.
So now I'm like, so they leave and I call my neighbor and she's like, do you need me?
Because I was going to leave, but I didn't leave.
I'm still in the car and I'm not leaving until they leave your property.
They're still outside chit chatting.
Listen, when I tell you I love a down ass white girl, she's sitting in a Honda Civic like, my dog.
So I was very, very pleased in that moment.
And let me just tell you, it's like, yeah, like, I mean, okay, I hit his car.
Like, that's not great.
Don't get me wrong.
But anytime we have to involve 12 for no reason, you're doing too much.
You're doing too much.
And the necessity that so many people feel to make something criminal is also too much.
I don't know if he thinks that he's going to, like, get more insurance for making a police report or whatever, but he's not.
And he would have been better off asking me just on the spot, like, hey, give me this much cash and we could call it.
That, that would have been even better.
I have done that before.
And let me tell you, it's great.
Why?
Well, I'll tell you why.
So now, I go, so now, I, um, I'm in the house and, hold on, I'm missing something.
And I get a call from the insurance company.
So the insurance company calls and she's like, hi, you know, um, we need to,
uh, file a claim.
I said, do it, ma'am, do what you got to do.
Um, so she said, well, I just need the number on the police report to put on the claim.
Um, and I said, no problem.
So, oh, absolutely a waste of paint.
I literally had to tell her, like, just so we're clear, I have pictures of the damage and his bumper has way more damage than what I caused.
So, just, let's understand that.
So now, I'm talking to this lady and she's just being, you know, she's just doing her job.
Like, asking me the right, the questions that she's supposed to ask and whatnot.
And then, this is not the right one, but it's going to work.
And then she says, do you have any more questions?
And I said, you know, I mean, you can't answer this, but, you know, I just get so frustrated at the fact that we just have to deal with this damn racket.
Because that's what this is.
This is a racket.
And she was like, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I don't know what you need me to say.
She was like, I'm sorry, I'm not sure what the question is.
And I said, no, no, it's not a question.
I'm just venting.
Because I'm, my insurance is about to go up, even though I'm paying insurance.
And it blows my mind every time that this type of thing happens.
Because it makes no sense.
Why am I paying insurance if when I have to use it, it's going to make my insurance go up?
And you know what she said, y'all?
Trust me, I feel you.
And that went so far.
She said, I understand, ma'am.
And I'm sorry.
I said, ooh, don't say sorry.
Because you know what?
It ain't us.
It's bigger than both of us.
It's not your fault.
And she was like, but I get you more than you know.
And it's so important to see people.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, just see people.
And what customer service is really about at this point is you having to serve as the goal between thieves and the people who are forced to have to engage with them.
All insurance is a thief, scam, Ponzi scheme, complete racket.
And we are forced by law to have to engage with it, which is just unprecedented nonsense.
Any type of insurance, whether it's for flight insurance or health insurance, all of this is nonsense.
And so I was really appreciative of her simply just seeing me in that moment and saying, I feel you.
And I was like, ma'am, I hope you have an incredible rest of your Monday, your week, your month.
Thank you for seeing me in this moment.
She said, no problem.
No problem.
And I wanted to, I just wanted to share that story because it really be the little things.
You know what I mean?
It really be the little things.
And the only time, the only reason I'll say pet insurance isn't a huge scam is because when my cat had a near death experience, it was only because I had pet insurance that I could afford to pay for it.
Really.
And the pet insurance is minimal compared to, you know, the exorbitant amount of, you know, car insurance, et cetera.
And like my, you know, don't get me wrong.
Again, all of this insurance is scammy whammy.
But it still was like, I mean, I got a really significant refund.
Now, mind you, I should have got more if it was based on their actual factual, but, you know, I can't even remember what kind of health insurance I use for the pet.
I think it's a part of progressive, which is also a scam.
So, um, this is my funny and black bonnet.
Everyone has told me that this is the best bonnet that they have ever used because it stays on at night.
So I just wanted to share that with you because I'm out here changing the bonnet game.
I'll take it.
Okay, this person ordered two of these.
Have I seen Jubilee debate Israeli versus 20 Palestine activists?
No, I'm not.
I'm not watching that.
That sounds just incredibly, um, I mean, kudos, kudos to the Palestine activists who joined that because that just sounds incredibly triggering.
Thank you, Irina.
What's up?
Over there in Kenya.
Irina, I'm about to put out some music and when I put it out there, I hope that you'll bring it to the Kenyans for me.
That's what I need y'all to really understand is that when I put out this music, the only thing that's going to make it helpful is if y'all share it.
I really hope y'all know that.
Like, because I don't got no record label or none of that.
I'm just going to be putting out vibes.
Do I have extra small for a two-year-old who can't seem to keep a bonnet on to save her life?
Unfortunately, no, I do not.
Was I triggered on the Jubilee show?
Um, yes.
At one point, yes.
They cut it out.
I told a nigga that if he didn't shut the fuck up, I was going to kick him out because he is evil.
And I meant it.
I meant it.
Someone asked me, how do I feel about I show speed being in the Caribbean?
I don't know anything about that young man, but I'll tell you this.
Anytime I see a young person kind of just being trotted around, um, I'm confused.
I'm concerned because, you know, his, his entourage is like 13 folks and, you know, they, they, they, they, it's just like the making of a celebrity.
And anything that's about the making of a celebrity, I'm going to look at sideways.
I love these pins.
How black am I going to have to get?
I, you know, that, and then I saw, um, Felakuti's son saying that, you know,
he met speed when he was in Nigeria and he was like, you know, I didn't like the vibes.
He was like, I felt like all of that was very, um, shady because he was like, I feel like they were in here trying to see where to put satellites and how they can exploit.
No, I don't have do rags, but that would be lit.
Um, so this week I am planning on releasing, so I wasn't even going to do this.
This is actually happening in like, um, I do have extra backings, but they don't, they're not standalone on the page, but I guess I should make them standalone.
Um, so basically what I was trying to say was, I don't know where this, so, okay, I was going to release in, in support of sexual assault awareness month.
I was going to release a free PDF version of the chapter, the unreleased chapter of my memoir that talks about my sexual assault, um, how I healed from it.
And also, you know, just provides some insights into how to be a supporter of somebody who has suffered through sexual assault.
However, when I started editing it, I realized it was so good.
I need to actually publish it, even if it's just published as an essay.
Okay, so, after I do this, I'm going to spend the rest of the day laying it out.
If I'm able to get this book laid out today, then I will actually put it out as a, um, as a physical piece of work.
And I will do that this week.
You know, the kind of artist I am is, I'm really, I just operate on vibes.
I know some, I know some people say that as a joke, but I really, that's how I operate.
Solely on vibes.
It's really like, oh, nah, you got to do this now.
Oh, you got to do this now.
It's not the best in terms of efficiency, but it's a, it's, it's a dream to be able to live like that.
And I don't use Amazon to put out books.
I use Lulu and you can only buy the book from me.
Two books.
Kima.
Um, I'll be right back.
I actually have small doses, which is my, well, I have my first self-published book, which is my poetry book.
Then I have small doses.
Then I have, what would the ancestors say?
And now I'm hoping to put out this little piece of work.
And what I would like to do is to just, whenever I fucking feel like it, put out sections of this memoir.
And over time, they will exist as individual pieces of work from, from an overarching series.
The series is Body Waving Through the BS.
And then one day, it'll be a whole volume.
This is how I should I be in here thinking about.
Where did I put the label?
This is what I be thinking about.
Fascists are not your friends.
Lapel pin.
So, I have like a massive audience.
We are in a time where money is tight.
So, I really appreciate anybody who chooses to spend, you know, their money on my work.
My work is, the goal of my work is to inspire.
And to encourage and inform.
No, because an audio, an audio record, okay.
An audio book is not some lightweight thing to do.
So, someone on here is suggesting, like, have you ever thought about doing an audio release part by part, then releasing the whole part, the whole book.
And, you know, an audio release is not just like a small feat.
For instance, like, I'm putting out the audio release of What Would the Ancestors Say.
And that right there is, it's a whole thing.
Now, am I going to do an audio release of each section?
Yes.
However, it's not as easy of a lift as I think people would think it is.
Um, my Patreon is $5 a month.
So, if you want to support me and support my work, you can subscribe to my Patreon.
It's $5 a month.
And, um, you know, like, I do stuff like this.
Like, when you're getting a pin from me, it's going to have, like, all the info of all of these greats on the back.
Right?
So, you're getting knowledge with it.
Like, the fascists are not your friends' pins.
They come with a little game.
And you have to match which fascist to their name.
Because you need to know who is running this country.
Um, you need to know who is in position to carry out the will of the evil that is behind the scenes.
You need to know the faces that they're using to do that.
Okay?
So, no, really though, where the label?
Where is the label at?
Where the label at?
Malika.
So, yesterday really drained me.
You know that meme from the reality show?
Ugh, today drained me.
That was me yesterday.
I tried to take a shower.
I tried to go to sleep and get my energy back.
Nope.
Never happened.
We did have an incredible author talk.
Um, that's kind of what I meant.
A certain tier of your Patreon can listen to the audio before the final book is released.
Kind of like a podcast special episode.
Oh, that's a good idea.
That's a great idea.
Um, that's something to think about.
Thanks for that.
All right, we have monthly author talks on Patreon for our Seal Squad book club, and we've been
really fortunate for the last two months to be able to have the authors of the books we
were actually reading in the book club to come on.
Um, and that is solely based on the fact that I'm dope.
That's why.
That's how he was able to get them to come through.
Why?
Because I'm dope.
So, they came through, and, um, last night we had Nanakwame Ajaybrenya, who joined us
to talk about his book, Chain Gang All-Stars.
And what I love is that our Seal Squad gets the opportunity to ask the authors questions
directly.
They're not simply just going through me.
And I really feel like, it may seem like a very, very small thing, but I'm trying to,
I'm trying to help bridge the gap where, there needs to still be reverence for artistry.
However, there's like this weird kind of like, um, celeb bubble that we put everybody in who
does anything.
And, we gotta stop it.
And we, it makes us also not know how to act.
So, it was really cool, and Nana's brilliant, and the book is brilliant.
So, if you haven't read Chain Gang All-Stars, you should go and do that.
Um, I'm brilliant because I just finished all of my packaging.
Everybody's getting their stuff.
Buh, buh, buh, buh, everybody's getting their stuff.
Buh, buh, buh, everybody's getting their stuff on top.
Putting out music.
My album, I'm gonna put it out on June 14th.
Mr. Marion, I don't play enough to say I play.
Can I read music?
Yes.
Can I sight read?
But like, can I like, just get down and be like, buh, buh, buh, buh, no, no.
So, I'm gonna put out this album.
And then every week, I will be doing what's called the Radical Rhythms Academy.
Where you'll get an opportunity to learn more about the song.
Because I produced all the songs.
So, I will explain the production choices.
I will explain my process in producing.
I can't even fucking believe I'm a producer.
I, and was like, because I sent him two more, no, three more records.
And he was like, hey, you did your thing on this.
I am, Iman.
I'm absolutely laughing at my ex.
He was like, you put your foot in this.
And it's all very uniquely you.
The creativity is all there.
Oh, Alan, I've produced many shows.
Um, okay.
Demo de Jesus.
So, he, my engineer, I don't think he knew, like, how much I really needed that.
Like, he was like, nah, like, you need, and then he was like, you need to do something where you're telling people about this.
And I was like, oh my God, that's already in my mind to do.
So, you saying that affirms it.
He was like, yeah.
Like, you need to explain to people how you chose these sounds.
Because this shit is, is interesting.
So, um, so, every week I'll be doing that.
And with some of them, there will be fundraisers.
So, for instance, for my song, Follestine, there will be a fundraiser.
Iman is in here right now.
So, there will be a fundraiser that will go along with that song.
Um, so, songs that, you know, I mean, all my songs are about some real shit.
But songs that are in particular aligned, we're going to be doing that.
I use Logic.
I know everybody uses Ableton.
Um, but I started recording my song, Psy Op.
I think I got a hit, y'all.
I got a hit.
I think I got a hit.
I think I got a hit, y'all.
Do y'all see how excited I am when I talk about music?
I do.
I think I got a hit, y'all.
Because I, I just love it.
It's, mm.
So, there you go.
And then y'all don't even understand the children's songs.
That I created for my children's show that's coming out in September.
That's going to be a vibe, too.
Yes.
So, excited about this.
Excited to be putting out things.
Excited to be making art for y'all.
Proud of myself for finishing up this, um, shipping.
So that y'all can send this stuff to your mamas on time.
Gonna head over and drop this off at the, um, post office.
And, um, yeah.
So, again, I came on here to just tell y'all, like, for my artists.
It don't, you, you don't got to do some big, you don't got to be doing a big, big operation
for it to have big impact.
Okay?
I gotta go.
I don't know who this dog barking at.
I don't know.
So good.
Bye.